https://www.whiteflowerfarm.com/privacy

Home
› Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Your Privacy
White Flower Farm respects the privacy of every individual who shops via our print or online gardening catalog. Our privacy policy was updated on June 17, 2014.
For our gardening friends who choose to receive our emails, rest assured we do not share, rent, or sell your email address to outside companies or agencies. Period.
We are members of the Direct Marketing Association. If you'd rather not receive mailings from other companies we exchange lists with, please email our customer service team at [email protected]. When you request our catalog online, you are given the opportunity to opt-out of having your postal address shared.
Your Personal Information
We save personally identifiable information when a visitor shares a page (when we seek opt in approval to access social data) or places an order (when we must save name, address, and credit card information in order to process the order) or request a catalog (when we use the name and address in order to deliver the catalog). In order to improve our website and identify navigation problems, we save information about how visitors click-through our site.
Your Security
Orders placed through our website utilize SSL (secure socket layers) to protect credit card information so it cannot be read in transit. If you do not have a browser that supports SSL or you are not comfortable sending your credit card information online, then you may call (1-800-503-9624), fax (1-860-496-1418), or mail (White Flower Farm, PO Box 50, Litchfield, CT 06759-0050) your order to us.
Our Use of Web Technologies:
In order to improve our site, products and services and provide more convenient, relevant experiences and advertisements to our customers, we and our service providers and partners may use "cookies," "web beacons," and similar web technologies to track your online activities. Cookies are small data text files that are stored by your web browser. Web beacons (also known as clear gifs or web bugs) are small, transparent, pixel-sized graphic images that are embedded in an HTML webpage, web-based document or email message and used to track when the page or email has been viewed.
Our Use of Targeted Advertising and Third-party use of Web Technologies:
We may also use third party advertising partners and service providers to deliver our ads to you that we feel may be of interest. To enable our advertising partners or service providers to serve ads to you, they may place a cookie on your browser or a pixel tag in an email to later deliver you an ad. They may collect and use information about your visits to this site in order to provide you with advertisements on other sites about our goods and services.  They may also allow third-party companies, including ad networks, to serve advertisements, provide other advertising services and/or collect certain information when you visit our website.
Third-party companies may:
use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visit to this web site in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you.
use non-cookie technologies to recognize your computer or device and/or to collect and record information about your web surfing activity including your activities on this website. These technologies may be used directly on this website. Please keep in mind that your web browser may not permit you to block the use of these non-cookie technologies, and those browser settings that block cookies may have no effect on such techniques.
use information such as mobile advertising identifiers, app usage, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked, and/or precise location data through this mobile app in order to provide advertisements about goods and services that are likely to be of greater interest to you.
Should you not be interested in these ads, you can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether or not to accept it. You may also disable cookies altogether. Please note that if you refuse to accept cookies, you may not be able to access portions of our site.
If you would like to erase all cookies at the end of every session or disable them entirely, please refer to your browser instructions on how to do so. Please note that disabling cookies will prevent you from placing items in your shopping cart, and you will not be able to order online. To order by phone, please call 1-800-503-9624 to reach one of our customer service associates. The Call Center is open from 9 a.m. to 5 p.m. Eastern Time Monday-Saturday and most Sundays from noon to 5 p.m.
Google Analytics for Display Advertising:
We have implemented the following features for Google Analytics for Display Advertising: Remarketing, Google Display Network Impression Reporting, DoubleClick Campaign Manager integration, and Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting. Using the Ads Settings, you can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize Google Display Network ads. If you would like to opt out of these programs, please visit Google Analytics' currently available opt-outs for the web.
To Opt-Out of Third Party Advertising:
You may manage your online profile and your opt-out choices by visiting the Digital Advertising Alliance or the Network Advertising Initiative, as well as Epsilon Targeting.
More Information:
For information about targeted advertising and cookies, please visit www.iab.net/privacymatters.
Get a free White Flower Farm Catalog
Save 10% on Gift Certificates over $50
Email Sign Up
Subscribe to enjoy gardening advice, email offers & more
Join Our CommunityKeep up with White Flower Farm on Social Media
